interesting.
面白い
scared.
怖い
I was a little embarrassed, so I thought I'd give it a try.
ちょっと恥ずかしいから、 しようかなと思って
I think it's good.
いいと思います
When was the last time you met your boyfriend?
最後に彼氏と会ったのはいつなの?
and,
と、
8 months ago.
8ヶ 月前
Did you have a hot night then?
その時は、 暑い夜を過ごしたんですか?
Be kind.
優しめる
Kind?
優しめの?
do?
やる?
When was the last time you did something naughty like that?
最後に そういう エッチいことしたのって いつなの?
The last time was about 2 months ago.
最後にしたのは 2ヶ月前ぐらい
Isn't he a handsome actor?
イケメン俳優でしょ?
No?
違うん?
Isn't it Johnny's Talent?
ジャニーズタレントとかじゃない?
What is it?
なんでしょ
誰?
What did you do with this wonderful person?
えらい人と 何したの?
What is the situation?
どういう状況?
I want to forget.
私忘れたい
Is it like that kind of borderline darkness?
そういう 境界の闇みたいな?
ERROR
あ、どういうんすか?
That's what it is.
そういうのあるんだ
Something for work?
仕事のため 的なこと?
I was made to work hard, telling myself that I had to work hard.
頑張らないと ダメだよって頑張らさせられました
Was there such a thing?
そういうのあったの?
ERROR
自分でさ したりするの?
Oh, are you going to do it?
あ、するの?
How do you do it?
どういう ふうにするの?
What, just try something, how do you do it?
どういう ちょっと何かやってみて どうやってやるの?
Where is it?
どこさあるの?
ERROR
分かんないからそういうの
ちょっと それ 分かんないんだけど どこにあるもんなの?
Just give it a try.
ちょっとやってみてよ
ERROR
分かんないんだもん
Is that a knee?
それは膝 膝?
It's not around here, right?
この辺じゃないでしょ?
Just point to me with your finger.
ちょっと 指で差し示してみて
What is that?
そ こは何?
What should I do?
どうする?
どう する?
To study, I wet my fingers and stroke them, eh?
勉強のために 指を濡らして ねえ なでる え?
Wet your fingers and it's a little hard. Don't stroke it. Try it.
指を濡らして なんか くいくい なでてはいけない やってみて
ERROR
やって みて やって み て って何?
Stroke?
なでる?
How strong does it seem?
どのくらい強そう?
So cute, so fucking cute
かわいいね、めちゃくちゃ めちゃくちゃかわいいね
I don't think so. Ah, that's right.
じゃない と思ってます あ、そうなんだ
ERROR
すごい エロい顔になってるよ 触るから
触 られるの?
Huh?
あれ?
ERROR
感じちゃう
of?
の?
ERROR
すごい 足きれい
She's so beautiful. She's definitely a model. Take care.
め ちゃめちゃきれいじゃん さすがモデルさんだね 気をつか
That's great. Food?
って えらいね 食事とか?
Yeah, I've started to be more careful lately.
うん 最近気をつかうようになりました あ、
That's right, for work.
そうなんだ 仕事のために
ERROR
あれ だね 食事とか気をつかっていると 匂いとかも 確認して
If you don't like it, you're a model.
お かないと 匂いちょ モデルさんだから
Anyone who smells like feet
足 だ匂いするって誰でも
It smells like roses. Why?
なんか バラ匂いがするよ なんで?
I wonder why
なんでだろう
That's a nice foot
や らしい足です
The producer made me do this.
こう いうのやってあげたの プロデューサーさん やらされた
I didn't do it for you. Oh, I was made to do it.
やって あげたの違うんだ あ、やらされたんだ
picture?
え?
what is this
何 これ
Isn't that an afterthought?
付 け付けじゃない?
ERROR
これ 付けてるよね
こんな の入ってるの?
Are you in charge?
任されてるの?
It's in
入ってます
It's cute, but it's already cute
可愛 い もう可愛いんだけど
ERROR
最 初 会った時すごいさ 精粗系なのかと思ったけど ドスケル
Dosukeru
で しょ ドスケル
De sho e
で しょ エ
You came here because you wanted to do something.
ンチ なこと したくて来てくれたんだよ
I felt sorry for her, so I kept playing with her.
か わいそうだったから かわいそうだったから ずっといじって
ERROR
く れてるじゃん 何?
I like chin chin
チンチン好きだね
ERROR
す げえ触ってるじゃん なん
Well then, everyone
で ね、ちゃんとみんな
ERROR
チ ンチン好きでしょ うん 好き?
Which do you prefer, beer or Chin Chin?
ビールとチンチンどっちが好き?
I was a little confused, do you like both?
ちょっと悩んだね どっちも好きなの?
You're touching me so much, don't look yet.
すごい触ってくるじゃん まだ見ちゃダメだよ
Look at me, you've been wearing such cute clothes for a long time. Favorite
こ っち見て すげえ可愛い服で ずっといたんだね お気に入り
I was surprised because I was dressed like this, wearing underwear.
の こんな格好だから びっくりしちゃった 下着を 向かって
Well, it's an unclip.
じゃ ん ア ンクリップやろ
turn back
後 ろ向いて
T-back
T バック
under the
の 下に
He's a really good guy.
め ちゃくちゃ良いやつしてる
Apparently
や らしい
...
I want to watch it forever...
ず っと見てたい...
Yeah ...
うん ...
Well then...
じゃあさ...
That's it...
もうそれさ...
Take it off... What if I take it off?
脱 い ... 脱いじゃえば?
It's hot, isn't it?
暑いでしょ?
Yeah...
うん...
Wow, amazing...
うわ、すごい...
hot...
暑い...
It's this hot
この暑いの
...
what?
何?
That's amazing, you definitely have abdominal muscles...
すごい ね、確かに、腹筋が...
Hey...
ねぇ...
It's so cute
ちゃくちゃ可愛いな
...
Gyu...
ギ ューってさ...
So cute...so cute...
可愛い...すげー可愛い...
Cute naughty...
可愛いやらしい...
Yeah ...
うん ...
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious...
美味しい...
Look, it's moving on its own.
ほら、自分で動いちゃってるでしょ
...
You want to take it off quickly, right?
早 く脱ぎたいんでしょ...
beautiful...
綺麗...
check...
チェック...
It will be checked...
チェックされるでしょ...
picture?
え?
Not done
されない
...
I'm really happy...
ちゃ くちゃ嬉しい...
picture?
え?
Himself
本人よ
...
Just a little...
ちょっと さ...
I want to see it from behind...
後ろから見たいからね...
Hold it in your body...
その 体に持って...
Are you dressed like Flowmetch?
フローメッチの格好してるの?
Yeah...
うん...
Look...
ほら...
I'm only looking at your butthole
お尻の穴だけ見てる
Yo...
よ...
Messed up...
めちゃくちゃ...
Do you have it?
持ち?
Hold...
持ち...
My hole...
自分の穴や...
Why do you hide it?
なんで隠すの?
No...
ダメだよ...
Now...
さぁ...
With both hands...
両手でさぁ...
Let me open the mango...
マンゴー開いてみせて...
It's beautiful...
綺麗だね...
Because I don't know
知らんから
...
Wow, that sounds low...
すごい 低く言ってるよ...
You did it...
やったね...
Because it's embarrassing
恥ずかしいから
...
what happened?
どう したの?
It's so Berber
すっごいベルベルだね
...
Awesome
す っごい
...
Bijobijo...
ビ ジョビジョ...
Bijo Bijo...
ビジョビジョ...
eye
め
You like it so much...
ちゃ くちゃ好きでしょ...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Take it away...
取り去って...
You have a nice body...
いい体してる...
hey
ね
...
Super beautiful
超 綺麗
...
You're so kind...
優 しいね...
Not too kind...
優しすぎない...
kind...
優しい...
good?
いい?
yeah?
ん?
So beautiful...
すっごい綺麗...
what happened?
どうしたの?
Awesome
すっごい
...
what happened?
どう したの?
I've only just put it in...
まだチンチン入れただけだよ...
Are you not moving it?
動かしてないの?
That's amazing
すごいね
...
Can I move it?
動 かしていい?
Looks dangerous...
やばそう...
Can I move it?
動かしていい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
copper?
どう?
Very tight
すっごいきつい
...
Close your legs...
足 閉じて...
It doesn't come...
か かってこない...
yes
そう
...
home?
う ち?
That's amazing...
すごいね...
hey...
ね...
Even though the current runs...
電流走っちゃうのに...
I can't move.
動けないね
...
It looks like you can't move
動 けなそうだね
...
Amazing amazing...
すごい すごい...
Would you do that?
そんなことしちゃうの?
That's amazing...
すごいね...
It's right here...
ここに当たっているでしょ...
It's tough when you hit here...
ここ に当たるときついんじゃん...
hey ...
ね ...
give me more
もっとたらして
...
It's so delicious...
め っちゃ美味しい...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Right here...
ここでしょ...
hey ...
ね ...
It's tough when you hit here...
ここに当たるときついんでしょ...
yes ...
はい ...
In the end
つまになって
...
Ah, it feels good
あー 気持ちいい
...
Honchi?
ほ んち?
yes ...
はい ...
Ah, it feels so good
あーすごい気持ちいい
...
Great, you're sleeping
すごい 寝てるね
...
It feels amazing...
すごい 気持ちいい...
Feels good
気持ちいい
...
Awesome...
すごい やばい...
Can I take it out?
出していい?
good?
いい?
I'm going
行くよ
...
Is this okay as an impression?
感 想としていい?
Yeah ...
うん ...
Do you understand?
分かる?
I understand...
分かる...
Do you understand?
分かる?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
amazing ...
すごい ...
It was amazing...
すごかったね...
I was shaking...
震えてたよ...
It felt good...
気持ちよかった...
That's what I did...
そうした...
I felt embarrassed...
恥ずかしくなっちゃった...
yes...
はい...